Let's do an unweighted accent with the hip.
Let's put our feet slightly apart.
Bend your standing leg.
Lift the heel of your unweighted leg and press the toe into the floor.
Make sure the ankle's in in our showgirl foot position.
The knee is coming off the hip and pointing forward slightly.
Pull that belly button in.
Lift your chest and relax your shoulders.
We're going to start by lifting the hip up and we're going to do a little step down in two parts.
So it's going to kind of catch your audience off by surprise cause you're going to go down and then down.
So you're going to really have to bend your standing leg.
So we're going to go drop it and then drop it a little further with also bending your leg at the same time.
So we're going to drop and drop.
Come up.
Drop and drop.
Very good.
Drop and then drop dipping down.
Drop.
Drip down.
Let's try it on the other side.
Just make your feet's in the right position first and everything is pulled up.
And your weight stays centered over your feet.
So we're going to drop and dip and drop and dip and drop and dip.
Good.
Make sure that everything stays nice and lined.
Don't lean forward on this and don't get too far back.
Make sure to practice this in the mirror.
Hand on both sides.